module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who is Fluffy?',
      a: 'Jane calls Sophie this way',
      b: 'hagrids dragon',
      c: 'Sarah Santa Cruzs brand new cat',
      d: 'a three-headed dog',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What power do the dementors have over other people?(Not the Corona Virus)',
      a: 'They drain them of all happiness',
      b: 'They make them go crazy',
      c: 'They mess with the stock market',
      d: 'They isolate everyone.',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who kills Professor Dumbledore?',
      a: 'Draco Malfoy',
      b: 'Sevrus Snape',
      c: 'Fenrir Greyback',
      d: 'Bellatrix Lestrange',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'How does Harry catch his first snitch?',
      a: 'In his mouth',
      b: 'with his broom',
      c: 'by sneezing',
      d: 'in his hat',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the mirror of Erised do?',
      a: 'predicts the future',
      b: 'Shows your hearts desire',
      c: 'helps detect viral diseases',
      d: 'makes you look ito the future',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who or What is Grwap?',
      a: 'Rons owl',
      b: 'Hagrids half brother',
      c: 'CHs new wi-fi password',
      d: 'Sirius house elf',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What caused Dumbledores hand to be shriveled?',
      a: 'old age',
      b: 'the corona virus',
      c: 'a ring',
      d: 'a death eater',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the half blood prince?',
      a: 'Lucius Malfoy',
      b: 'Tom Riddle',
      c: 'Harry Potter',
      d: 'Sevrus Snape',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Why does Snape protect Harry?',
      a: 'James was his best friend',
      b: 'He was in love with Lily',
      c: 'He is Harrys real father',
      d: 'He honestly had nothing better to do',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Why would you have a harry potter trivia in 2020?',
      a: 'author could not come up with a better topic',
      b: 'author is currently reading this to her 6 yr old ',
      c: 'any topic is fine for a spare trivia',
      d: 'All of the above',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};